<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dntiontk.github.io</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on dntiontk.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RSS Feed aggregation</title>
      <link>/posts/rss-feed-aggregation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rss-feed-aggregation/</guid>
      <description>This post is related to my previous post about civic code. I mentioned that there are multiple RSS feeds that the city maintains, and that this data is not particularly easy to find and parse.
We are going to create an RSS feed aggregator creates a weekly summary and automatically creates a new post on this blog.
The data First, we need to identify which feeds we&amp;rsquo;ll be using. For now, we are going to keep the list small, however we expect that there will be more sources as time goes on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>civic code</title>
      <link>/posts/civic-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/civic-code/</guid>
      <description>I frequently find myself on the City of Windsor website. I&amp;rsquo;ll scroll through city council meeting agendas and videos, browse the open data catalogue, check for newsroom headlines; annoyed by how outdated it feels the entire time. This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the look of the site either. I don&amp;rsquo;t really care about the asthetics. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about it feeling like the site is intentionally disjointed and built in a way to make engagement a little bit harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Black software developer based in Windsor, Ontario, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my thoughts and experiences with you.
As a DevOps/Platform Engineer, I&amp;rsquo;m all about automation and making things run smoothly. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with a ton of different technologies over the years, but I&amp;rsquo;m especially into Kubernetes and all the cool things you can do with it.
In my work, I&amp;rsquo;ve tackled a bunch of different challenges, from scaling to security to performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>